http://www.tizag.com/about/privacy.php

Privacy Policy Statement
This is the web site of Tizag.com.
We can be reached via e-mail at Tizag Contact.
This Policy is effective on March 31st, 2009
Logged Information
For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer's IP Address, domain name, but not the e-mail address (where possible).
We collect the domain name, IP Address, and e-mail address (where possible) of visitors to our Web page,
the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what
pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit.
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.
The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, disclosed when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting
an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Web site and applicable laws or
to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Web site and Aggregate visitor data is used when to describe user statistics for Tizag.com (page views, unique visitors, etc).
Cookies
With respect to cookies: We do not set any cookies.
With respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies
that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server
companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information.
For further information, consult the privacy policies of: advertising.com, tribalfusion.com, google.com/adsense.
Google Adsense and DART
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
Privacy Policy Changes
From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information
practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the
ability to opt out of these new uses.
If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically, we will
post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and we will use for these new purposes only data collected from the time of the policy change
forward. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.
Google.com
Tizag Supporters
2003-2005 Erack Network | Copyright | Privacy Policy |
Advertising Information
